<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: health | NightShiftDev]]></title>
  <link href="http://nightshiftdev.github.com/blog/categories/health/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://nightshiftdev.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2016-10-06T07:11:10-05:00</updated>
  <id>http://nightshiftdev.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[nightshift]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[<del>"GroceryPro is back"]]></title>
    <link href="http://nightshiftdev.github.com/blog/2015/02/19/grocerypro-is-back/"/>
    <updated>2015-02-19T07:35:00-06:00</updated>
    <id>http://nightshiftdev.github.com/blog/2015/02/19/grocerypro-is-back</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I am sorry to announce that the GroceryPro project have been abandoned. There is NOT going to be any further development on GroceryPro.</p>

<p><del>
New GroceryPro in development!</p>

<p><del>
We believe "you are what you eat". The food industry bombards us with artificial products, preservatives and foods based on GMOs.</p>

<p><del>
This is why we decided to start working on a new version of GroceryPro; one that will take the app to the next level!</p>

<p><del>
The new GroceryPro will take care of you and the planet, and encourage you to make healthier decisions. It is going to be about:  fast, intelligent list creation, organized shopping, healthy, balanced meals and a happy planet.</p>

<p><del>
Some of the new “technical” features will include:</p>

<ul>
<li><del>Storing lists and recipes in the cloud </li>
<li><del>User to user list and recipe sharing</li>
<li><del>Easy way to follow users, or rather, their meal recipes ;)</li>
<li><del>Convenient ways to create grocery lists from recipes</li>
</ul>


<p><del>
We are planning to make the application FREE (ad-based).</p>

<p><del>
If you are looking for a revolutionary, interactive shopping list, we hope the new GroceryPro will be your number one choice.</p>

<p><del>
Stay tuned for more GroceryPro dev news!</p>

<p><del>
P.S. We have 1000 beta testing spots available, so let us know if you’d like to take part in the
development of GroceryPro. If you are interested, send us PM on <a href="https://facebook.com/GroceryProApps">facebook</a> or e-mail us at <a href="&#x6d;&#x61;&#x69;&#108;&#116;&#111;&#x3a;&#103;&#114;&#111;&#99;&#x65;&#114;&#x79;&#112;&#x72;&#111;&#64;&#103;&#109;&#97;&#105;&#108;&#46;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;">&#103;&#x72;&#x6f;&#x63;&#101;&#114;&#121;&#x70;&#114;&#111;&#64;&#x67;&#109;&#97;&#x69;&#108;&#46;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;</a>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
